https://www.mrpayday.ca/policy.shtml

Get Up To $1,500! Apply Now!
Privacy Policy
At Mr. Payday your privacy and confidentiality of your personal information are protected within our business, whether provided through paper based, electronic communications or on the telephone. We are committed to protecting your privacy and providing a secure online experience. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to transmit and store information about you. When you enter your personal information on our online application, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL), thereby offering the highest level of encryption or security possible. This means you can rest assured that communications between your browser and this site’s web server are private and secure.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU
We collect personal, financial and other information from you in order to for us to conduct the business of providing you with approval for a payday loan. We may collect further information from references that you provide as well as your financial institution and other service providers. We will limit the information we collect to what is needed for that purpose.
INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE ABOUT YOU
We do not disclose any information about you except when it is required by law or for the purposes that it was collected for. Disclosure, as permitted by law, may involve the sharing of your personal information with other parties for the purpose of assisting in the process of providing you with approval for a payday loan. We might share your personal information with affiliated third parties for the purpose of providing you with a payday loan.
SECURITY
At Mr. Payday, security is taken seriously. We have implemented and maintain high security standards and procedures to safeguard against unauthorized access to your information. We employ appropriate measures to protect consumer information against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These may include encryption, physical access security and other appropriate technologies. Mr. Payday continually reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary.
COMMUNICATION VIA EMAIL
Mr. Payday may send you information to inform you of your account status, updates, changes, product-related announcements, or special news and information we believe you will find useful. If you wish to be removed from our email list, please send your request to: unsubscribe@mrpayday.ca
LINKS TO OTHER SITES
Mr. Payday may provide links to third party websites. Mr. Payday is not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by websites that are linked from our website. For this reason, if you link to another website from Mr. Payday, please consult that website’s privacy policy.
OUR RIGHT TO CHANGE
We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our site. If you have any questions on our privacy policies and procedures please contact us at: privacyofficer@mrpayday.ca
GET THE CASH YOU NEED WITH OUR INSTANT ONLINE PAYDAY LOAN
RELOAN
APPLY
TOLL FREE PHONE
1-877-432-2274
TOLL FREE FAX
1-866-435-2271
Connect with Mr. Payday on Social Media.
Copyright © 2020. All Rights Reserved.
Home
About Us
Requirements
Articles
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Menu
Home
About Us
Requirements
Articles
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Implications of non paymentFinancial implicationsMr. Payday is a responsible lender. All delinquent accounts are subject to an interest rate of up to 59% APR depending on your province. All returned pre-authorized payments are subject to a NSF fee of up to $50 depending on your province.Collection practicesWe collect delinquent loans using all legal remedies available including legal debt collection and civil court action.Impact on Your Credit ScoreFailure to repay your loan will result in information regarding your delinquency or default on your account being reported to a third party consumer reporting agency, which impact your credit score.* Application processing times might change without any further notice. During our regular business hours and when the services are available.
